[
  {
    "question": "Operational costs",
    "answer": "The various monetary requirements associated with the day-to-day running of a business.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "f6ddac94-5b30-4c3a-9262-139397a1c6df"
  },
  {
    "question": "High-intensity interval training (HIIT)",
    "answer": "An exercise training method defined by intervals of near-maximal intensity broken up by relatively short rest periods.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "96dc8745-2b50-4925-a442-60e7ef7a3a7b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Adherence",
    "answer": "The level of commitment to a behavior or plan of action.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "87cd68f6-ed30-479f-bbd8-19637168dbdc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Prospect",
    "answer": "An individual who has been identified as a potential client.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "b6b01c66-031b-418a-ae86-1f54f62f3303"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sales process",
    "answer": "A system for learning about the needs of a potential client to be able to identify and present a number of solutions for those needs.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "1a773132-5d7a-48b5-bbf9-2f7251921da7"
  },
  {
    "question": "Open-ended questions",
    "answer": "Nondirective questions that can’t be answered with a simple yes or no answer; they require critical thinking to formulate a response.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "fcfcf725-888e-4744-940e-f1050bc194ab"
  },
  {
    "question": "Working the ﬂoor",
    "answer": "A rapport-building technique where fitness professionals walk around the gym floor talking to members without overtly presenting a sale.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "9b4972ad-0972-48a1-8424-cf08a20981ad"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rapport",
    "answer": "A relationship in which two people understand each other’s ideas, have respect for one another, and communicate well.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "75975300-fc66-4df7-b3bf-935a5e66ca2d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Forecasting",
    "answer": "A business management technique that helps predict how much work is needed to meet a revenue goal.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "f4d21cb7-eb66-40a6-9737-c02996e00c29"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unique selling proposition (USP)",
    "answer": "Highlighting unique skills or traits during a sales presentation that allow an individual to stand out from the competition.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "8c34e0c3-eafa-421a-9602-89d17ec6726f"
  },
  {
    "question": "Brand",
    "answer": "A product or service identified by specific, unique characteristics.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "d89482f7-cc06-4627-963e-5d6a33328966"
  },
  {
    "question": "SWOT analysis",
    "answer": "A professional development technique that helps individuals identify their personal strengths and weaknesses, opportunities for growth, and potential threats to success.",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "chapter 2"
    ],
    "id": "4b993591-a564-443f-8bb5-56aab6aff8ee"
  }
]